{
    "users": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Which built-in method returns the character at the specified index?",
            "correctanswer": "charAt()",
            "options": [
                "charAt()",
                "getCharAt()",
                "CharacterAt()",
                "None of the above."
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "How many days are there in a year?",
            "correctanswer": "window.print();",
            "options": [
                "window.print();",
                "browser.print();",
                "navigator.print();",
                "document.print();"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "Which built-in method reverses the order of the elements of an array?",
            "correctanswer": "reverse()",
            "options": [
                "changeOrder(order)",
                "reverse()",
                "sort(order)",
                "None of the above."
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "Which of the following function of Boolean object returns the primitive value of the Boolean object?",
            "correctanswer": "valueOf()",
            "options": [
                "toSource()",
                "valueOf()",
                "toString()",
                "None of the above"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "Which of the following function of String object splits a String object into an array of strings by separating the string into substrings?",
            "correctanswer": "split()",
            "options": [
                "slice()",
                "split()",
                "replace()",
                "search()"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "Which of the following function of String object creates a string to be displayed as bold as if it were in a <b> tag?",
            "correctanswer": "bold()",
            "options": [
                "anchor()",
                "big()",
                "blink()",
                "bold()"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed in a small font, as if it were in a <small> tag?",
            "correctanswer": "small()",
            "options": [
                "link()",
                "small()",
                "sup()",
                "sub()"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "Which of the following function of Array object removes the last element from an array and returns that element?",
            "correctanswer": "pop()",
            "options": [
                "pop()",
                "push()",
                "join()",
                "map()"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "Which of the following function of Array object applies a function simultaneously against two values of the array (from right-to-left) as to reduce it to a single value?",
            "correctanswer": "reduceRight()",
            "options": [
                "pop()",
                "push()",
                "reduce()",
                "reduceRight()"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax to print a page using JavaScript?",
            "correctanswer": "window.print();",
            "options": [
                "window.print();",
                "browser.print();",
                "navigator.print();",
                "document.print();"
            ]
        }
    ]
}